KAHO SHIBUYA

FRONTEND DEVELOPER REACT DEVELOPER

	https://kahoshibuya.dev/
in	https://www.linkedin.com/in/kaho-shibuya/
()	https://github.com/shiv-chan
\square	kshibuya31@gmail.com
_	

SUMMARY

Aspiring frontend developer with a specialization in React development. A highly passionate learner and be currently on 4+ projects. With 3+ years of experience as a digital marketer, I'm interested in user experience, promoting, and monetizing web services. My professional background enables me to develop the product from a business standpoint as well and can differentiate me from the other developers. It also enhances collaboration with the marketing & business teams and eventually leads to optimal frontend applications.

C 604-499-7851

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Go-to Pomorodo - A customizable pomorodo timer with BGM

Tech Stack: React, Redux, YouTube IFrame Player API, Styled Components, Material UI

Weather App - A weather app with a search and a beautiful design

Tech Stack: React, Redux/Context API, Weather API, Sass

To-do App - A to-do app with a sort and drag&drop feature (light&dark theme)

https://react-todo-app-snowy.vercel.app/
https://github.com/shiv-chan/react-todo-app

Tech Stack: React, Redux, Sass

EXPERIENCE

Web Designer / Web Developer

Puppy Time Vancouver | Apr 2021 - Aug 2021

- Designed the company website from scratch contents and its layout, theme.
- Developed the website with HTML, CSS and added some features with JavaScript.
- Collaborated with the marketing team and created the website SEO strategy-wise.

Online Advertising Operation

sann, Inc. | Oct 2019 - Dec 2020

- Supported sales team with building ad campaign strategies by analyzing clients' past performances or marketing trend data.
- Reported the results and suggested the next actions to the clients, which led to continuous contracts and incremental revenues.
- Created tools that reduced human-errors by ~90% and automated repetitive duties with Google products such as Spreadsheets or App Script.

EDUCATION

Cornerstone International Community College of Canada

Diploma, Web and Mobile App Development | Jan 2021 - Present

- Focus on web development
- Related courses: Computing, Algorithms, Problem-solving, OOP, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Node.js

Sprott Shaw College

Diploma, Business Admin Sales & Digital Marketing with Honours | Feb 2015 - Jan 2016 | GPA 4.14

- Focus on marketing and sales
- Related courses: Bookkeeping, Accounting, Customer Services, Web design, SEO
- Practicum at Okanagan Boys and Girls Clubs as Digital Marketing Assistant